ushow.media 2016-06-12

# IT'S ME | OWN YOUR STAGE!

Privacy Matters

It'sMe! takes privacy of Internet users seriously. Your privacy is the highest priority to us. To help protect your privacy we provide this overview explaining our online practices and the options you can choose regarding the data and information collected. This form applies to all information collected from or submitted to our mobile application (the "App"). 

The Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting your personal data is to provide you with the services you requested and with those we believe will optimize and enhance your use of our App and related services. Providing us with your information is not a requirement for using our App, Service, but note that if you choose not to provide us with certain information, we may not be able provide certain services or functionality of the App and/or Service.

There are a number of different ways that we may collect personal information from you:  
\- Registration: When you register to use our Service, we receive certain information about you through Facebook, Twitter or Google+, as applicable to your method of registration. This information, as indicated during the connection process may, include your name, your activities, hometown, interests, likes, user location, your photos and videos, website, email, phone number, friends, online presence, social following and other. This registration process is optional for It'sMe users who only wish to view videos, but is required for users who would like to broadcast via It'sMe or to use the Service's more advance options.

\- Communication from You: When you contact us with questions, concerns or for purposes of customer/technical support, we collect the information contained in your message, which may include your name, contact details and any other personal information you provide.

\- Surveys and Promotions: From time to time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or sweepstakes (any of these a “Promotion”) via our Services. If you participate in a Promotion we will request certain Personal Information from you. We use the Personal Information you provide to us in these instances to administer your participation in the Promotion. Participation in a Promotion is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

\- Aggregate Information: Whenever you enter our App our web server automatically collects and aggregates information with respect to your visit. This information includes URLs or domains of referring websites, browser type, operating system, the pages that you access and the date and time of your visit. In general this aggregate information will not identify you personally, but if we do correlate such information to you, we will treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

How We Use Information

We may use the information provided to us to:  
\- Contact you from time to time with critical user or service updates or other information important for our services, or for the support of the service you requested. We may contact you to ensure that the information we have in our records is still correct and to add additional information to complete your profile;

\- Receive feedback from you and inquire about any features you would like to see in future products. We may also contact you to ask you about our products and also to inform you of upgrades, technical issues, promotions and new products that you may be interested in;

\- Send out newsletters to you with articles and information which we believe may be of interest to you;

\- Customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;

\- Evaluate users, their preferences and trends for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, which we may use for marketing purposes and with respect to operations and development;

\- Compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties;

\- Prevent activity we determine to be potentially illegal;

\- Enforce this Privacy Policy and/or our Terms or any other purpose referenced herein or therein.

Information you voluntarily transmit via the Service is publicly accessible and may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We do not control such uses of your personally identifiable information, and by using the Service, you assume the risk and acknowledge that the personally identifiable information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties and by us for any number of purposes and that the usage restrictions set forth in this Privacy Policy do not apply.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required to do so by law or when necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Service, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm, financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. We may also disclose your personal data to enforce our policies or respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the right of others. In all cases, such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your information with:  
\- A third party performing services on our behalf that has agreed to keep such information confidential (such as excluding threats from potential cyber attacks or trolls or other security purposes, the processing of your credit card payment, if applicable, or the conduct of an online survey, for example), including our partner, Maker Studios, to provide you with benefits as part of our It'sMe benefit program. Maker Studios will keep such information confidential.

\- One of our partners, but only if you've requested this in advance. Please note that in such cases, this Privacy Policy will not cover their information practices and we will not be responsible for the privacy practices exercised by any such partners.

\- Business Transfers: The information that is collected by It'sMe is considered to be an asset. In the event that It'sMe, any affiliated company, division or portions of its assets are acquired by another company, such information may be one of the transferred assets. We will take reasonable steps to place a notification of such a transfer on our Site and in the App.

Security

We take reasonable technical and organizational measures to guard against unauthorized or unlawful processing of the information collected and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your personal data. While no system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our Service reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

Information received via Facebook Connect is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). This ensures that your information is secure as it is sent over the Internet to our server. Furthermore, we have implemented procedures to ensure that your information is only made available to such designated staff as necessary to carry out the stated purposes that we have communicated to you.

In addition, we recommend that you do your part in protecting yourself from unauthorized access to your account by ensuring no one else uses your machine when you are logged in, by logging off from the Site when it is not in use and by keeping your password confidential.

We destroy personal information once there is no longer a legal or business need for us to retain it.Personal information will be destroyed PERMANENTLY by using such methods as stated below:

(a) Personal information that is documented on paper will be shredded or incinerated.  
(b) Personal information that is saved in the form of electronic files will be destroyed by technical means making the records non-reproducible.

Links to other sites

We may offer links from our App to other websites which may be hosted by our partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites, including Facebook, Twitter and Google (through which you must register for the It'sMe Service) are not governed by this Privacy Policy and It'sMe makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. It'sMe is not responsible for how third party websites use and share your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

Our Policy toward Children

This Service is a general audience Service which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of thirteen (13). In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, in accordance with our Terms, children under the age of thirteen (13) are not permitted to access or use the Service, and children under the age of thirteen (13) should not provide any personal information to the Site or the App. We ask that parents supervise their children while online and/or using mobile devices.

Contacting us

Any requests for access to your information, modification of your information or questions in respect of this Privacy Policy should be sent to the following email address support@ushow.media.
